[
  {
    "questionNo": "Q1",
    "question": "Which of the following numbers is odd and composite?",
    "options": ["11", "15", "9", "Both B and C"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q2",
    "question": "Which of the following numbers has an odd number of factors?",
    "options": ["4", "9", "16", "All of the above"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q3",
    "question": "Which of the following is the only even number that is not composite?",
    "options": ["0", "2", "4", "6"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q4",
    "question": "Which of the following numbers cannot be expressed as a sum of two odd primes?",
    "options": ["10", "16", "18", "9"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q5",
    "question": "How many even prime numbers are there between 1 and 100?",
    "options": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q6",
    "question": "Which of the following is a pair of co-primes but not twin primes?",
    "options": ["(13, 15)", "(29, 31)", "(3, 5)", "(17, 19)"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q7",
    "question": "Which of the following sets contains only composite numbers?",
    "options": [
      "1, 4, 6, 9",
      "4, 6, 8, 10",
      "4, 7, 8, 10",
      "6, 9, 11, 12"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q8",
    "question": "Which number must be added to both 27 and 36 to make the resulting numbers co-prime?",
    "options": ["2", "3", "5", "1"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q9",
    "question": "What is the minimum number that must be subtracted from 81 to get a prime number?",
    "options": ["6", "4", "2", "1"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q10",
    "question": "Which of the following prime numbers forms a twin prime with a number less than it?",
    "options": ["29", "17", "11", "5"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q11",
    "question": "Which of these numbers is smallest odd, composite, and not co-prime with 15?",
    "options": ["35", "17", "21", "33"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q12",
    "question": "Which of the following statements is not always true about co-prime numbers?",
    "options": [
      "Their product is always odd",
      "Their common factor is 1 only",
      "One of them could be even",
      "They may both be primes"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  }
]
